

## Profile

I'm not only passionately interested in development, but also in discussing new ideas, trying out new perspectives, and tackling new challenges.

Able to code for several hours and enjoy every second of it, but also a fan of going out, getting fresh air, bringing rhythm to life, so that new thoughts come into his head.

Enthusiastic about being able to use my skills to create exciting tools, I have the opportunity to learn from others and pass on knowledge. In this way, amazing experiences and results can be achieved by combining different ways of thinking.

# Employment History

Cloud Migration & Imp Delivery Analyst at Accenture Cloud Services GmbH, Dresden, Deutschland

May 2019 — Present

Consultant and lead developer for a systems integration project.

#### **Tasks**

- Development of interfaces to integrate different systems with a ServiceNow platform.
- Responsible for concept design, development, testing, and go-live phase.
- Creation and refinement of PBIs.
- Management of the development team.

# **Technologies**

· ServiceNow, Javascript, REST, SOAP.

#### Software Development at Allware, Valdivia, Chile

March 2018 — September 2018

Software Development for the "New Businesses and Products" Department.

## **Tasks**

- Development lead of a platform to automate the analysis and processing of accounting information.
- Junior developer within a web development project for the livestock industry.

#### **Technologies**

- Python, MongoDB, NLP, Machine Learning.
- Laravel, Javascript.

## Internship at Fraunhofer IKTS, Dresden, Deutschland

April 2017 — June 2017

Trainee in the IT department at the service desk as support and access rights management during the implementation of the 8MAN solution.

### **Details**

Dresden, 01788871236 jaimefvs@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth 09.10.1993 Temuco, Chile

Nationality Chilean

#### **Skills**

Python

C++

Natural Language Processing

Machine Learning

Javascript

MongoDB

React

Django

#### Languages

Spanisch

Englisch

Deutsch

#### **Hobbies**

Woodworking, playing guitar, and sports.

# Education

# Computer Scientist, Universidad Austral de Chile, Valdivia, Chile

March 2012 — October 2018

# **Thesis**

## Title

Monitoring for the Sophia Platform's Thematic Classifier and Concept-Drift Impact.

## Description

Development and proposal of the first concept to solve the concept-drift problem within the classifier of the platform. Integrate a statistical analysis for the text data into the platform and create a workflow to identify potential problems with the classifier.

# Exchange Student, Technische Universität Dresden, Dresden, Deutschland

July 2016 — July 2017

DAAD exchange program for engineering students.

# **1** References

**Nelson Soto Osses from Allware** 

nsoto@allware.cl

Matthieu Vernier from Universidad Austral de Chile

matthieu.vernier85@gmail.com